jhon anderson puentes hernandez



apxanderson02@gmail.com



3052433991



linkedin.com/in/jhon-anderson-puenteshernandez-32118420b



https://jhon2410.github.io/portafolio/

Summary

https://jhon2410.github.io/portafolio/

I have experience applying the MERN development stack, sufficient knowledge in different programming languages such as Java, Python, PHP, JavaScript. I am familiar with the most famous layout patterns like MVC. agile methodologies such as SCRUM, XP. 2 years of experience working on own projects and small commissions. Intermediate level of English.

spa management, reactive pages and communication to endpoints of the rest api, and relational and nonrelational databases.

GITHUB: https://github.com/Jhon2410

Technologies I have used:

- > Javascript
- > Typewritten text
- > React
- > Vue
- > Angular
- > Node is
- > Java
- > PHP
- > Laravel
- > Django
- > Flask
- > Express
- > Boostrap 5
- > Sass less
- > tailwind
- > quasar
- > Ajax (axios, search, jquery)
- > GraphQI
- > Jsonwebtokens
- > MongoDB
- > MySql
- > Postgresql
- > Hit
- > HTML5
- > CSS3
- > Git and GitHub
- > Heroku

Experience



Full-stack Developer

Profesional independiente

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

Frontend Web Developer

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

Education

Universidad Surcolombiana

Ingeniería, Ingeniería de software Aug 2019 - Jun 2024

Licenses & Certifications

METODOLOGIA DE LA PROGRAMACION DE SISTEMAS INFORMATICOS -

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9210002460334CC1004343925C

* APLICACION DE LA CALIDAD DEL SOFTWARE EN EL PROCESO DE

DESARROLLO - Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9123002460258CC1004343925C

- DESARROLLO WEB CON PHP Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9123002459879CC1004343925E
- Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) SCRUMstudy Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile
 895219
- Six Sigma Yellow Belt 6sigmastudy The global certification body for six sigma certifications 846233
- **G** Fundamentals of Search Marketing Google Digital Garage NHS HBK CWE

Skills

Ingeniería • Resolución de problemas • Software Development • Web Development • Design Patterns • Investigación • Estrategia • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB